Okay so now we're going to look at the hair, so for this mix up three tones,
going to look for something a bit like a mid tone, then we're going to mix a
hair tone, something darker and then we're going to mix a slightly lighter tone
and then we're going to mix a flash tone, okay then we're going to combine
those tones, going backwards and forwards, also a hair tone, I'm just going to look at that, okay
first we're going to oil in, just taking some oil, okay oiling in, just going to mix a pay
something for the case around the temple, now just going to mix a violet
and some black, probably a bit more and some black, going to reinstate this
so there's a full value, then we're going to look for this second tone,
so maybe something in between violet-orange, that down a bit, be okay, it's looking for this
these shapes, the transition, okay, something a bit lighter, something in between,
going to go for this orange and violet, a bit more yellow in there, something around there,
we're going to take that mid, get that hair and that into the
sat fringe, then I'm just going to take the alka shape, just a hairline,
very low in the brush, every time you make a mark, you're going to take the
scalp, something for the scalp there, between the blizzard and the green,
back a little bit more, these highlights now, okay, just going backwards and forwards with the
hair, look at this, okay, we're going to come in with a lighter, we need some of these,
it's an even lighter version, just looking at these transitions, and now I'm just going to look around
this edge, just work into that edge, something a bit lighter, okay, so I'm going to call that the,
I'm going to call that the front of the hair for a second, your little highlights here,
I'm going to get too involved with all this, I'm going to put too much information in there,
kind of on the, a bit more yellowy violets, and then maybe burnt umber, yellow violets,
so just oil in first, just all ink in, okay,
probably just pick out some of these light shapes and that's, that's it really,
so call it some yellow violets, just turn that down, a lot darker, what we think,
okay I'll start with the mid-violet, some of the yellow, what happens there, okay,
yellow, it's only down some burnt umber, even darker again, maybe this was just burnt umber,
it's burnt umber yellow, touch of violets, okay yeah, so more on the burnt umber, yellow side,
okay, I'm going to look at some of these darker shapes, say burnt umber violets,
red touch of yellow, something slightly in between, now these highlights,
doing too much now, all of this, I'm going to leave that now, that's the hair finished, that's done.